The way I dealt with this, which kind of actually worked in this case, and I still don't know exactly why
Is that I created something called a Wi-Fi wall of shame, which is basically, I said to the developers, okay, here's a wall
Every time you have any problem with Wi-Fi
write that the time… the date and time you had the problem with the Wi-Fi and stick it on the wall.
And
Within a couple of days, this wall was completely creaking with
Post-its saying that kind of like, you know, I had problems with the Wi-Fi, I had difficulty with the Wi-Fi, etc.
We'd been kind of reporting through all of the normal channels to
To kind of say, look, you can't really do this project
Unless you have a connection to the Internet, that's pretty basic. And we got nowhere
But this kind of way
Which I know there's a quote from Jerry Springer, which I'm kind of like ambivalent about as a scrum master, but I think I think it might be right. It might be good guidances. He says, I don't solve people's problems. I televise them
And I think that's kind of what I was doing here. I wasn't solving the problem because I tried to solve the problem and completely failed. So I ended up just televising it, ended up shouting about it
As loud as I could. And mysteriously, it got fixed. I still don't know what happened to fix it